Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Civil Rights Serials TAM.771
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Civil Rights Serials
1923-2003
1960-1979
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
American Civil Liberties Union
TAM.771
7 Linear Feet in 10 manuscript boxes and 11 flat boxes
The Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Civil Rights Serials contains over 240 titles on civil rights and civil liberties in the United States (US) and Europe in the 20th century. The collection dates between 1923 and 2010, with the bulk of the material dating from the 1960s through the 1970s. Topics include the civil rights movement in the US in the 1960s, issues surrounding civil liberties for racial and religious minorities in the US and Europe in the mid to late 20th century, and the work of the American Civil Liberties Union in these areas.
Arrangement
Serials in this collection are arranged alphabetically by title.
Conditions Governing Access
Open to users without restriction.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This collection combines serials relating to civil rights drawn from two discrete groups of material held by the Tamiment Library. The first was a partially inventoried backlog of serials, received by the library through donations, subscriptions, and in archival collections. The second group consisted of around 1,700 serials, newspapers, and magazines, organized by title as an artificial collection, referred to as Periodicals.001 or Boxed Newspapers. This material was combined, inventoried, and arranged and described in subject-based categories in 2017. The accession number related to this collection is 2017.049.
Scope and Contents
The Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Civil Rights Serials contains over 240 titles on civil rights and civil liberties mainly in the United States (US) in the 20th century. The collection dates between 1923 and 2010, with the bulk of the material dating from the 1960s through the 1970s. The bulk of the collection consists of serials published in the US, with some titles published in Canada, France, the United Kingdom, Poland, Germany, and China. Large runs of publications include Black Panther Community News and the American Civil Liberties Union's Civil Liberties. Topics include the civil rights movement in the US in the 1960s, issues surrounding civil liberties for racial and religious minorities in the US and Europe in the mid to late 20th century, and the work of the American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU) in these areas. The majority of serials in this collection focus on civil rights for African Americans in the US with serials from the ACLU, the Black Panthers, and the Southern Poverty Law Center on this issue. Other topics include issues surrounding censorship and civil rights for Jewish people in the Soviet Union.
Civil rights -- Periodicals.; African Americans -- Civil rights -- United States.; Civil rights movements -- United States.; Black power -- United States -- 20th century.; Black Panther Party
- 49th State Compass: The 49th State Movement, Chicago, IL, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- "By Any Means Necessary!": New Afrikan People's Organization, Atlanta, GA, circa 1970s (Box Shared Tamiment 052, Folder 22)
- 'Holocaust' News: Revisionists' Reprints, Manhattan Beach, CA, circa 1960s (Box Shared Tamiment 052, Folder 24)
- A.S.A. Speaks: Afro-American Student Association, Brooklyn, NY, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Abuses of the Military Chaplaincy: American Civil Liberties Union, New York, NY, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Action Bulletin: Civil Rights Congress, New York, NY, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Activist: Newspaper of the ACT for Disarmament Coalition: ACTIVIST Collective, Toronto, Canada, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- ADC Background Paper: American-Arab Anti-Discrimination Committee, Washington, DC, Undated (Box 13, Folder 27)
- ADC Issues: American-Arab Anti-Discrimination Committee, Washington, DC, Undated (Box 13, Folder 28)
- ADC Reports: American-Arab Anti-Discrimination Committee Research Institute, Washington, DC, 1982-1984 (Box 12, Folder 4, Box 13, Folder 29-30)
- Afram Newsletter: Centre d'Etudes Afro-Americaines et des Litteratures du Tiers Monde Anglophone, Paris, France, 1976-1978 (Box 12, Folder 5-6)
- Africa Retort: Africa Research Group, Cambridge, MA, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- African Spirit: Office for African American Student Services, New York, NY, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- African World: Youth Organization for Black Unity, Washington, DC, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- African World: Youth Organization for Black Unity, Greensboro, NC, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 2-4)
- Afro-America: Panaf Publishing Association, Brooklyn, NY, 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Afro-American Affairs: The Resource Center of the Center for Afro-American Studies, Athens, OH, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Afro-Americans for Halstead and Boutelle Newsletter: Young Socialist Alliance, New York, NY, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Afro-Americans in the Far West: Far West Laboratory for Educational Research and Development, Berkeley, CA, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Against Discrimination: Chicago Council Against Racial and Religious Discrimination, Chicago, IL, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- American Civil Liberties Union News: American Civil Liberties Union of Northern California, San Francisco, CA, 1957-1963 (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
- American Civilization on Trial: News and Letters Pamphet, Detroit, MI, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- American Negro: The American Negro; Chicago, IL, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- American Revolution: Pages from a Negro Worker's Notebook: Monthly Review Press, New York, NY, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Amerika: News from Nowhere, DeKalb, IL, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Annual Report: Urban League of St. Louis, Inc., St. Louis, MO, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Anti-Racist News: Anti-Racist News, Columbus, OH, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- ARA Net Bulletin: ARA Network, Minneapolis, MN, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- ARA News: Anti-Racist Action, Columbus, OH, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Arm the Masses: December 12th Movement, New York, NY, 1992-2002 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Arm the Masses: The Harriet Tubman, New York, NY, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
- bail-out: Steve Kurzyna, New York, NY, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Beek: Pisemko o Prawach Zwierzat: Man Gala Press, Sopot, Poland, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Bill of Rights Newsletter: Constitutional Rights Foundation, Los Angeles, CA, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Black America: Revolutionary Action Movement, New York, NY, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Black Autonomy: Black Autonomy Collective, Seattle, WA, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Black Conscience: Organization for African-American Education, Detroit, MI, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Black Economy: United National Publishing Co., Inc., Chicago, IL, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Black Force: Charles Kenyatta, New York, NY, Undated (Box 13, Folder 7, Box 21, Folder 11)
- Black Informer: The Black Informer, Yonkers, NY, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Black Labour: Black Workers Alliance, Toronto, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Black Liberation: Black Liberation Journal, Inc., New York, NY, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Black Liberation: Radical Education Project, Ann Arbor, MI, Undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Black Nation: Getting Together Publications, Oakland, CA, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Black New-Ark: Black New-Ark, Newark, NJ, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 11-13)
- Black Newark: Black People of Newark, Newark, NJ, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Black Panther: The Black Panther Party for Self Defense, Oakland, CA, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Black Panther: Black Community News Service: Black Panther Newspaper Committee, Berkeley, CA, 1969, 1991-1995 (Box 2, Folder 2, Box 7, Folder 5-6)
- Black Panther: Black Community News Service: The Black Panther Party, Oakland, CA, 1968-1970 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Black Panther: Black Community News Service: The Black Panther Party Ministry of Information, San Francisco, CA, 1967-1970 (Box 7, Folder 7-12, Box 8, Folder 1-6)
- Black Panther Community News: Black Panther Collective, New York, NY, circa 1970s, 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 1, Box 13, Folder 10)
- Black Panther Intercommunal News Service: The Black Panther Party, Oakland, CA, 1971-1979 (Box 2, Folder 3, Box 8, Folder 7-8)
- Black Political Agenda: Black Political Agenda, Washington, DC, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Black Political Review: Black Political Review, Detroit, MI, 1966-1968 (Box 13, Folder 12-13)
- Black Power Bulletin: Afro-American Unity Movement, Detroit, MI, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Black Scholar Book Club: Black Scholar Book Club, Sausalito, CA, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Black Shame: Black Shame, Munich, Germany, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Black Star: Afrikan People's Party, New York, NY, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Black Student United Front: Black Student United Front, Detroit, MI, 1971-1976 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Black Unity: Black Unity, Vista, CA, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Black Vanguard: Black Vanguard, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Black Voice: Leroy Butcher, Montreal, Quebec, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Black Youth Internationale: New Rochelle Chapter of the O.A.A.U., Inc., New Rochelle, NY, circa 1970s (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Black-World-View: Institute of the Black World, Atlanta, GA, Undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Break de Chains: National Committee for the Defense of Joanne Chesimard & Clark Squire / Come! Unity Press, Harlem, NY, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Brief: Illinois Division, American Civil Liberties Union, Chicago, IL, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Bulletin: Civil Rights Congress, Pittsburgh, PA, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- By Any Means Necessary!: New Afrikan People's Organization, Atlanta, GA, 1984-1990 (Box 2, Folder 8-9)
- CAIFI Newsletter: Committee for Artistic and Intellectual Freedom in Iran, New York, NY, 1977-1978 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- CCR News: Center for Constitutional Rights, New York, NY, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Censored News: Civil Rights Congress, New York, NY, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Censorship News: A Newsletter of the National Coalition Against Censorship: New York, NY, 1991-1994 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Center for Constitutional Rights: Center for Constitutional Rights, New York, NY, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Chi-Core News: Committee of Racial Equality, Chicago, IL, 1946 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Civil Liberties: American Civil Liberties Union, New York, NY, 1963-1995 (Box 2, Folder 10-15, Box 3, Folder 1-2, Box 8, Folder 11-14, Box 9, Folder 1-12, Box 14, Folder 7-8, Box 15, Folder 11, Box 21, Folder 6)
- Civil Liberties: American Civil Liberties Committee, Bristol, CT, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Civil Liberties Alert: American Civil Liberties Union / Washington Office, Washington, DC, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Civil Liberties in New York: New York Civil Liberties Union, New York, NY, 1951-1971 (Box 3, Folder 3, Box 14, Folder 9-10, Box 15, Folder 13)
- Civil Liberties Law Review: Harvard Civil Rights, Cambridge, MA, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Civil Rights and American Society: Young Peoples Socialist League, New York, NY, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Civil Rights Bulletin: IUE-CIO, New York, NY, 1952-1954 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Civil Rights Bulletin: Labor Committee to Combat Intolerance, Bridgeport, CT, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Civil Rights Monitor: Leadership Conference Education Fund, Inc., Washington, DC, 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Civil Rights Story: The American Jewish Committee, New York, NY, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Civil Service Leader: Civil Service Leader, New York, NY, 1967-1970 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Clarion: C.U.N.Y. Professional Staff Congress, New York, NY, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Clarion Call: The Clarion Call, Cincinatti, OH, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- CLSA Reports: Commission on Law and Social Action, New York, NY, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Committee Against Racism: Elect C.A.R. Slate: International Committee Against Racism, Brooklyn, NY, Undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Committee Against Racism: National Report: C.A.R. Committee Against Racism, Storrs, CT, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Common Cause: Boston Labor Committee to Combat Intolerance, Boston, MA, 1947 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Common Cause: Jewish Labor Committee, New York, NY, 1946 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Common Ground: Alaska Common Ground Collective, Juneau, AK, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Common Ground: UC Santa Barbara, Santa Barbara, CA, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Common Ground: Common Ground, San Diego, CA, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Concurrent Nationalism: Committee For Political Development, Philadelphia, PA, Undated (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Contac: Essence of Life: Afro-American Cultural Center, Storrs, CT, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Convergence: The Christic Institute, Washington, DC, 1984-1988 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Courage is Contagious: The Bill of Rights Versus The Un-American Activities Committee: Citizens Committee to Preserve American Freedoms, Los Angeles, CA, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- CRC Reporter: Civil Rights Congress, Philadelphia, PA, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Crossroad: Spear & Shield Publications, Chicago, IL, 1987, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Crusader: Garland Publishing, Inc., New York, NY / London, UK, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 12-13, Box 15, Folder 1)
- Crusader: Robert F. Williams, Peking, China, 1964-1969 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- CRV: Repression, Rebellion, Revolution: Committee of Returned Volunteers, New York, NY, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- CRV / NY: Committee of Returned Volunteers, New York, NY, Undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
- CURE: Citizens United for Racial Equality, San Diego, CA, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Death to the Klan!: Death to the Klan!, New York, NY, 1983-1986 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Death to the Klan!: John Brown Anti-Klan Committee, Chicago, IL, 1980-1982 (Box 16, Folder 5, Folder 6)
- Democracy and the Negro People: Negro History Week Bulletin, Washington, DC, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Democracy and the Negro People: Negro History Week Bulletin, Washington, D.C., 1947 (Box Shared Tamiment 052, Folder 23)
- Dialectics of Black Power: Weekly Guardian Associates, New York, NY, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Docket Report: Center for Constitutional Rights, New York, NY, 1983-1986 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Doing Democracy: Center for Living Democracy, Brattleboro, VT, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Eagle Eye: National Democratic Party of Alabama, Huntsville, AL, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Eros Free: Society for the Emancipation of Sex in America, Minneapolis, MN, Undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Extra: Extra, Chicago, IL, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Faith: Black Allied Student Association, NYU, New York, NY, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Fear, Frustration, Backlash: The New Crisis in Civil Rights: Jewish Labor Committee, New York, NY, Undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Feature Press Service: American Civil Liberties Union, New York, NY, 1958-1968 (Box 16, Folder 11-13)
- First World: First World Foundation, Atlanta, GA, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Free Angela: Newsletter of the San Francisco Committee to Free Angela Davis and the National United Committee to Free Angela Davis: NUCFAD, San Francisco, CA, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Freedom Now: New Stage in the Stuggle for Negro Emancipation: Pioneer Publishers, New York, NY, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- From the Soapbox: International Committee Against Racism, Madison, WI, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Front: Florida Free Press, Talahassee, FL, Undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Fund for the Republic Bulletin: The Fund for the Republic, New York, NY, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- Garvey's Voice: The Universal Negro Improvement Association and African Communities League, Philadelphia, PA, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Genius of Huey P. Newton: Ministry of Information, Black Panther Party, San Francisco, CA, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Global Views: Global Views, San Francisco, CA, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Grassroots: Black Liberation Front BLF, London, UK, Undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Hammer and Steel Newsletter: Hammer and Steel, Boston, MA, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Harlem Cultural Review: Harlem Cultural Council, Inc., Harlem, NY, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Harlem Liberator: Harlem Liberator, New York, NY, 1934 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Highlander Collections: Highlander Research and Education Center, New Market, TN, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Info: West Germany: New York Committee for Civil Liberties in West Germany, New York, NY, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Inner-City Voice: League of Revolutionary Black Workers, Detroit, MI, 1970 (Box Shared Tamiment 052, Folder 25)
- Internal Discussion Bulletin: Sojourner Truth Organization, Chicago, IL, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Introduction to the Black Panther Party: Radical Education Project, Ann Arbor, MI, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Inventory of Research in Racial and Cultural Relations: Committee on Education, Training and Research in Race Relations of the University of Chicago, Chicago, IL, 1948-1952 (Box 16, Folder 15, Box 17, Folder 1-3)
- Ironbound Voices: Ironbound Information Center, Newark, NJ, 1983-1986 (Box 17, Folder 5-8)
- IUE-CIO Civil Rights Bulletin: IUE-CIO, n.p., 1953 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- IUE-CIO Civil Rights Report: IUE-CIO, n.p., circa 1960s (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Jihad News: Jihad News Service, Philadelphia, PA, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Joint Newsletter on Intergroup Relations: Committee on Desegregation, New York, NY, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Joint Newsletter on Intergroup Relations: Committee on Desegregation and Integration/Society for the Psychological Study of Social Issues, New York, NY, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Journal of Intergroup Relations: Nairo, New York, NY, 1958-1960 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Juche: Juche, Cambridge, MA, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Justice: Commission for Social Justice, West Hampstead, NY, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Justice at Home and Peace Abroad: Black Liberation Commission c/o Line of March, Oakland, CA, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Keep Strong: Keep Strong Publishing Company, Chicago, IL, 1976-1980 (Box 18, Folder 3-6, Box 19, Folder 1-2)
- Labour Action: Amnesty International Canadian Section (English Speaking), Ontario, 1993-2000 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Law for the People: National Lawyers Guild, New York, NY, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Liberation News: Black Liberation Party, Jamaica, NY, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Life of Martin Luther King Jr. in Photographs: United Federation of Teachers, Undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
- like it is!: National Anti-Racist Organizing Committee, Seattle, WA, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Malcolm: Radical Tradition and a Legacy of Struggle: Cooperative Research Network, New York, NY, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Malcolm X's Message to White Revolutionaries: Litho Reproductions, Nottingham, UK, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Minorities / Minorias: Minorities / Minorias, New York / New Jersey, 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Montclair State College Committee Against Racism Newsletter: International Committee Against Racism, Montclair, NJ, Undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Movement Support Network News: MSN News, New York, NY, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Mundt Ferguson Nixon Versus America's Freedom: Civil Liberties Union of Massachusetts, Boston, MA, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- My Fight Is in the Ghettos of Philadelphia Not in Vietnam: W.E.B. DuBois Clubs of America, New York, NY, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- N.Y. Civil Liberties: New York Civil Liberties Union, New York, NY, 1992-1995 (Box Shared Tamiment 052, Folder 26)
- NBIPP Newsletter: National Black Independent Political Party, New York, NY, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- NY Newsletter: Committee Against Racism, Brooklyn, NY, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- NAACP Newsletter - Illinois Youth Division: NAACP - Illinois Youth Division, Chicago, IL, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- NAROC: National Anti-Racist Organizing Committee, Oakland, CA, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- National Boycott News: Institute for Consumer Responsibility, Seattle, WA, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- National Boycott Newsletter: National Boycott Newsletter, Seattle, WA, 1984-1987 (Box 4, Folder 7-8)
- National SNCC Monthly: Student National Coordinating Committee, New York, NY, 1967-1969 (Box 10, Folder 4-5)
- Negro as an American: Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, Washington, DC, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Negro Champion: American Negro Labor Congress, Chicago, IL, 1926 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Negro History Week Bulletin: International Workers Order, New York, NY, 1946 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Negro in America Today: National Labor Service, New York, NY, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Negro Leader: Negro Leader, Uniontown, AL, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Network: National Urban Coalition, Washington, DC, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- New Afrikan: Ministry of Information, Harlem, NY, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- New Afrikan Freedom Fighter: National Committee to Defend New Afrikan Freedom Fighters, New York, NY, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- New Dimensions...New Challenges: American Civil Liberties Union, New York, NY, 1965-1967 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Newark...: Black Mask, Newark, NJ, Undated (Box 19, Folder 20)
- News of the Hawaii Alliance: The Hawaii Alliance, Honolulu, HI, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Newsletter: New York Civil Liberties Union, West Chester, NY, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Newsletter: Anti-Bakke Decision Coalition, San Francisco, CA, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Newsletter: Black Women's United Front, Newark, NJ, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Newsletter: Chicago Alliance Against Racist & Political Repression, Chicago, IL, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Newsletter: Western Pennsylvania Committee for Protection of Foreign Born, Pittsburgh, PA, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- No KKK - No Fascist USA!: The John Brown Anti-Klan Committee, San Francisco, CA, 1989-1992 (Box 4, Folder 11, Box 20, Folder 9)
- NSM: Northern Student Movement, New York, NY, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- NY Civil Liberties: New York Civil Liberties Union, New York, NY, 1974-1992 (Box 4, Folder 14-19, Box 5, Folder 1-8)
- OMOWE: Undergraduate Student Assembly Howard University, Washington, DC, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- On the Ideology of the Black Panther Party: Ministry of Information, Black Panther Party, San Francisco, CA, Undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
- On the Prowl: Anti-Racist Action, Toronto, Ontario, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Open Forum: American Civil Liberties Union, Los Angeles, CA, 1929-1932, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Painted Poetry Appreciations: Shut-In Publication, Tuskegee, AL, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Pamoja Venceremos: Venceremos Publications, East Palo Alto, CA, Undated (Box 5, Folder 11-12, Box 6, Folder 1-2, Box 10, Folder 6-10)
- Pamoja Venceremos: Together We Will Win: Pamoja Venceremos, Palo Alto, CA, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 11-13)
- Partners for the Future: The Southern Poverty Law Center, Montgomery, AL, 1993-1996 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- People's Champion: Patterson Defense Committee, New York, NY, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- People's Community News: Black Community Information Center, Mount Vernon, NY, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- People's Tribunal: Mobilization Committee Against Police Brutality, New York, NY, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Phylon Review of Race & Culture: The Atlanta University, Atlanta, GA, 1954 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Police Power and Citizens' Rights: American Civil Liberties Union, New York, NY, Undated (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Police Spying in Michigan: Police Spying in Michigan, Detroit, MI, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- The Political Economy of Black Power: Queens College, Flushing, NY, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Political Rights Defense Fund: Political Rights Defense Fund, New York, NY, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Presence Africaine: Presence Africaine, Paris, France, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- Privacy Report: Project on Privacy and Data Collection / American Civil Liberties Union Foundation, Washington, DC, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 24)